Front-End Developer



□ PORTFOLIO http://cherylcodes.com

ABOUT ME

My name is Cheryl Leung. I am a Front-End Developer with a passion to develop great. functional, aesthetically beautiful and accessible websites while also providing a great UX/UI experience.

I have always thrived working with people, due to my many years in client/customer related employments. I bring these skills with me as a developer along with a strong set of technical skills.

I am very excited to join a collaborative team and to continue to grow my personal and technical skillsets.

EDUCATION

HackerYou College of Technology **Web Development Immersive** 2019

University of Guelph **Bachelor of Applied Science** 2010 - 2014

CONTACT

647-290-2772

✓ leung.cheryl@icloud.com

github.com/leungcheryl

@cherylcodes

WORK EXPERIENCE

The Co-Operators - Jan 2016 - Jan 2019

Licensed Insurance Representative

- o Team Captain/Lead (Jan 2017)
- Mentor (Feb 2017)
- Utilized multiple computer systems on a daily basis obtained strong technical skills specifically in the AS400, Excel, Outlook and sales database systems
- Assessed and underwrote coverage based on individual client's needs, company's Underwriting Guidelines and in accordance with Financial Services Commission of Ontario (upheld my RIBO License at the highest standard)

Notable Achievements

- Employee of the Month ('LIR of the Month') award out of 250 employees in October 2017 for overall sales and performance achievements
- Placed Number 1 out of 200 employees for sales results out of all service employees with 30 sales (goal is 8 sales/month) in August 2018
- Obtained a leadership role within one year as a Team Lead (Team Captain) of 11 brokers; helped & gave constructive feedback to senior and junior brokers and organized creative events and competitions within the team
- Obtained a leadership role as a Mentor in the mentorship program, mentoring other brokers and trained them on AS400 system, insurance guidelines and regulations, endorsements and customer service
- Averaged a 98.5% audit score on all policies audited.
- Organized and lead whole office competitions as one of the main leads on the Captains Team - the most recent being the lead for 'HB's Disneyland', a trivia based competition to boost morale for all 21 teams (250 people)

Tory Burch LLC - May 2015 - Feb 2016 Sales Support Associate (Cash Lead)

- Interacted with hundreds of customers daily, responding to inquiries, resolving complaints and performing cash transactions
- Took a leadership role as a "cash lead", being one out of four sales support associates with a management password
- Closed tills at the end of the night, monitoring and balancing cash as well as prepared bank deposits and withdrawals using the POS system.

TECHNICAL SKILLSET

- + HTML5
- + CSS₃
- + SASS
- + Javascript ES6
- + jQuery + React
- + API's
- + Responsive Design
- + Accessibility
- + Team-based development
- + Version Control and Collaboration using Git and GitHub
- + Using VS Code, Sublime, snippets, Emmet
- + Paired programming + Project Scope Management
 - + AS400
 - + Best Practices